<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- This is an automatically generated file. -->
<TitlePage>
  <Title>
    AssociationSchemes
  </Title>
  <Subtitle>
    A &GAP; package for working with association schemes and homogeneous coherent configurations
  </Subtitle>
  <Version>
    2.0.0
  </Version>
  <Author>
    John Bamberg<Alt Only="LaTeX"><Br/></Alt>
<Address>
John Bamberg<Br/>
School of Mathematics and Statistics<Br/>
The University of Western Australia<Br/>
35 Stirling Highway<Br/>
Crawley WA 6009, Perth<Br/>
Australia<Br/>
</Address>
<Email>john.bamberg@uwa.edu.au</Email>
<Homepage>http://school.maths.uwa.edu.au/~bamberg/</Homepage>

  </Author>
  <Author>
    Akihide Hanaki<Alt Only="LaTeX"><Br/></Alt>
<Address>
Akihide Hanaki<Br/>
Department of Mathematics<Br/>
Faculty of Science, Shinshu University<Br/>
Matsumoto 390-8621, Japan<Br/>
</Address>
<Email>hanaki@shinshu-u.ac.jp</Email>
<Homepage>http://math.shinshu-u.ac.jp/~hanaki/</Homepage>

  </Author>
  <Author>
    Jesse Lansdown<Alt Only="LaTeX"><Br/></Alt>
<Address>
Jesse Lansdown<Br/>
School of Mathematics and Statistics<Br/>
The University of Western Australia<Br/>
35 Stirling Highway<Br/>
Crawley WA 6009, Perth<Br/>
Australia<Br/>
</Address>
<Email>jesse.lansdown@research.uwa.edu.au</Email>
<Homepage>http://www.jesselansdown.com</Homepage>

  </Author>
  <Date>
    2 February 2022
  </Date>
  <Abstract>
    AssociationSchemes is a GAP package for working with association schemes and homogeneous coherent configurations.
  </Abstract>
  <Copyright>
    &copyright; 2019 - 2022 John Bamberg, Akihide Hanaki, Jesse Lansdown<P/>

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.<P/><P/>This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.<P/><P/>You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.

  </Copyright>
  <Acknowledgements>
    The third author would like to acknowledge the support of an Australian Government Research Training Program (RTP) Scholarship while writing this software. The first and third authors are also grateful for the 2019 CMSC Retreat for providing an opportunity and environment for some of the founding work on the package.
  </Acknowledgements>
  </TitlePage>